KHARIS GOLDMAN

PROFILE

I am a full time college student at Eastern Washington University studying Visual Communication Design in my Senior Year. I have great leadership skills. I am friendly and outgoing, kind, responsible, and punctual, I would love to intern at Propaganda Creative and learn more about design and working in the professional world at a design firm. I am interested in digital design, print design, branding, and website design and have experience in these fields as well as proficient in Creative Cloud programs and photography. I hope to work for a design firm upon graduation in the spring and think having real world experience will be beneficial to me. Even though i do not have experience in professional design, other than some work for family and friends, i have an extensive background working. Thank you for your time and consideration.

EXPERIENCE

Community Service, **Covenant Shores** 2003-2004

- •Visited with the elderly.
- Helped Organize Parties and Events.
- Cooked and helped with food.

Babysitter, Donica Mischler 2005-2006

> took care of children and friends, cooked dinner, picked up child from school, tutoring, cleaning, and fun activities.

Cashier, Baskin Robins

June 2006-November 2006

- •Take orders, scoop ice cream, and cashier.
- •Clean and close store
- Lettering on cakes

Front Desk, Club Emerald December 2006-April 2007

- Receptionist
- Clean equipment
- Data Entry

- Cashier
- Daycare

Server, Covenant Shores June 2007-May 2008

- •Set up
- Server residents in dining hall
- Deliver Orders to rooms

Server, Aramark May 2008-August 2009 May 2010-August 2010

> ·Server in VIP area and beer garden.

Barista, On Alert December 2011 - Sept 2013

- Open and close stand
- Create yummy drinks
- Cashier

Server, The Hampton Inn June 2015 - Present

- •Cook
- Server
- Draw and Hand-letter signs for the bistro

GET IN TOUCH

(206) 458 - 1808

kharisgoldman@gmail.com

AVAILABILITY

mon/wed - 1145a - 230p, after 530 tues/thurs - before 1p, after 5p fri/sat/sun - all day

EDUCATION

Mercer Island High School Mercer Island, WA High School Degree 2008 GPA: 3.8

Eastern Washington University

Cheney, Wa Major: VCD

Minor: Computer Science Degree: In Progress Core GPA: 3.73

References

Travis Masingale (509) 359 - 2437

Mindy Breen (509) 359 - 7002

P. Colin Manikoth (509) 359 - 4086